smith-wessonforum.com 2018-12-16

# Intermarkets Privacy Policy - Intermarkets Inc.

_Revised July 20, 2018_

Intermarkets, Inc. is an online advertising management services firm that offers advertisers opportunities to display their interactive ads on/in websites, emails, and other digital platforms that are included within the Intermarkets Portfolio or affiliated companies, including any online or mobile website, application (“app”), or other digital product or service installation through which this Privacy Policy appears (each a “Service,” collectively the “Services”). Our services streamline the selection and delivery of interactive ads for advertisers and website publishers.

Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to protecting the personal information you share with us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, protect, and share information when you are served an advertisement using or visiting the Services. This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information preferences.

By using the Services, you consent to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Intermarkets does not own, control, manage, or employ.

Intermarkets uses the following ad servers and their privacy policies can be found by clicking on their names below:

While we are not a member, we are committed to following the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Self-Regulatory Principles](https://www.networkadvertising.org/code-enforcement/).

### Information We Collect through the Site

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, username, email address, credit card details, and other information as we may from time to time request at our discretion (“Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII”) if you choose to share such information with us. For example, you may be asked to provide us with certain Personally Identifiable Information when you register with or use our Services, sign up for an email subscription, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register with or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content, features, or services available on or through the Services. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Intermarkets service, such as service announcements, administrative messages, special promotions, and Intermarkets newsletters, which are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We automatically collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information when you use the Site. Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes demographic information (such as age, gender, city or state) and a user’s click stream information. Click stream data is anonymous and can include information such as your IP address, webpages viewed, the date and time at which those pages were viewed and interaction with content and advertisements on those webpages. Technologies used to collect this click stream data include cookies and web beacons. Intermarkets collects Non-Personally Identifiable Information and stores it in log files. We use this information to help us understand how people use our Site. For example, each time you use the Site we automatically collect the type of web browser you use, your operating system, your ISP, which pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Site.

We may supplement our click stream data with Non-Personally Identifiable Information (namely, behavioral and demographic data from third party Services Providers as defined below) to target and serve some of the advertisements you see on the Services and those of our Portfolio publishers. This anonymous supplemental data may include such things as zip code, age, gender, and income range. We use the Non-Personally Identifiable Information described above to better customize the sort of advertisements you see. This information also may be used to help measure and research an advertisement’s effectiveness, or for other purposes. We also aggregate anonymous cookie data in order to identify large audience segments that assist advertisers in targeting their campaigns to the most relevant Internet audience.

While we encourage third party advertising providers to comply with applicable law and self-regulatory standards, there are far too many online advertising transactions occurring on our Portfolio publishers’ websites to police every transaction. We pass through all advertising disclosures and opt-out mechanisms of the advertising providers, but the use and collection of information by our third-party advertising Service Providers is governed by the individual privacy policies of those providers.

**Social Media Information**

If you visit the Services on a device on which you also use social networks or if you interact with us through a social media service or other platform, we may have access to some information you provide to that social network or platform such as your name, email address, friend list, photo, age, gender, location, birthday, social networking ID, current city, and the people/sites you follow, or your posts or “likes.”  For a description on how social media services and other third-party platforms, plug-ins, integrations or applications handle your information, please refer to their respective privacy policies and terms of use, which may permit you to modify your privacy settings.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser), web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage), and other similar technologies to improve the quality of the Services and to better target and analyze consumer behavior with the goal of providing better and more relevant advertising. Our cookie does not include your name or anything personal to you. It simply tells us that we have encountered your computer at some prior point. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Alternatively, you are always free to opt out of the cookies.

Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. If you would like more information about these practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/index.asp).

### How We Use and Share Information Collected through the Services

**General**

We use Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information for internal purposes only, such as to notify you of new products or services, to send service notifications, to customize the advertising and content you see, to offer email promotions from our trusted network of partners (which you may opt-out of at any time, as described more fully below), to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve the Services, to conduct research, to solicit your feedback and input about the Services, and to provide more relevant and effective products, services, and advertisements on or through the Services.

Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be combined with data collected from other sources so that we may further improve the relevance and effectiveness of products, services, and advertisements offered on or through the Services. We will not sell, share, or rent Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to third parties, without your permission, except as expressly disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

**Service Providers**

Intermarkets may share Personally Identifiable Information with its service providers that help Intermarkets provide the services that you request (“Service Providers”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as credit card processing, advertising, analytics tools, data management services, web hosting, and web development. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services, however, each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information Only**

We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information regarding the Site (e.g., number of visits, page views, and the like) without your permission. However, such information does not identify you individually.

**Other Transfers**

We may share Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Intermarkets. If Intermarkets is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Sharing**

We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information regarding the Site (e.g., number of visits, page views, and the like) without your permission. However, such information does not identify you individually. As for Personally Identifiable Information, we may share your first name, email address, zip code, and party affiliation with our trusted network of partners. However, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of sharing such information.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Intermarkets cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. Intermarkets reserves the right to disclose Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of Intermarkets or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

### Email Opt-Out Procedure

**IF YOU DO NOT WANT TO RECEIVE EMAIL PROMOTIONS FROM OUR TRUSTED NETWORK OF PARTNERS, YOU MAY UNSUBSCRIBE FROM OUR EMAIL NEWSLETTERS OR PROMOTIONAL EMAILS BY FOLLOWING THE OPT-OUT INSTRUCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE EMAIL OR EMAIL US AT[INFO@INTERMARKETS.NET](mailto:INFO@INTERMARKETS.NET) AND YOU WILL BE REMOVED FROM OUR THIRD-PARTY DISCLOSURE LIST.**

Once a request to opt out has been received, Intermarkets will send a confirming email message to the user that the user’s Personally Identifiable Information has been successfully opted out of Intermarkets’ database. If you do not receive this confirmatory email, then please contact us to ensure that your request was received and processed.

### Cookie Opt-Out Procedure

Intermarkets and our service providers may use the information we collect from and about you to deliver relevant ads to you when you use the Services (on any of your devices) or another service. As noted above, third-party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and information the different devices you use and your activity on such devices, to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about interest-based advertising and third-party entities that use these technologies, please go to <https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/>.

**IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO OPT OUT OF INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING, PLEASE VISIT  [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)  or [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).**

_**PLEASE NOTE** that if you erase or otherwise alter your browser’s cookie file (including upgrading certain browsers) you may need to opt out again._

_**PLEASE NOTE** that opting out of the ad-serving cookie does not mean that you will stop seeing either pop up advertising or banner ads embedded in websites. You can control many pop ups by using free software available on the Internet or by disabling JavaScript on your browser. Intermarkets has no control over the use or frequency of pop-up ads employed by website publishers or software manufacturers. _

### Mobile Opt-Out Procedure

We also sometimes use, or partner with publishers, publisher-facing, or app developer platforms that use mobile Software Development Kits (“SDKs”), or use an SDK with a mobile app that we offer, to collect Information, such as mobile identifiers (e.g., IDFAs and Android Advertising IDs), and information connected to how mobile devices interact with our Services and those using our Services. A mobile SDK is the mobile app version of a web beacon (see “Web Beacons” above). The SDK is a bit of computer code that app developers can include in their apps to enable ads to be shown, data to be collected, and related services or analytics to be performed. We may use this technology to deliver or help our Partners deliver certain advertising through mobile applications and browsers based on information associated with your mobile device.

Depending on your device, you may be able to reset your mobile device’s advertising identifier at any time by accessing the privacy settings on your mobile device. In addition, each operating system, iOS for Apple phones, Android for Android devices and Windows for Microsoft devices, provides its own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application advertisements. You may review the support materials and/or the privacy settings for the respective operating systems in order to opt-out of tailored in-application advertisements.

**IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO OPT-OUT OF SUCH AD NETWORKS’ AND SERVICES’ ADVERTISING PRACTICES ON THE PARTICULAR DEVICE ON WHICH YOU ARE ACCESSING THIS POLICY, GO TO[HTTP://WWW.NETWORKADVERTISING.ORG/MOBILE-CHOICE](http://www.networkadvertising.org/MOBILE-CHOICE) TO OPT-OUT FOR YOUR MOBILE WEB BROWSERS. YOU MAY ALSO DOWNLOAD THE APPCHOICES APP AT [HTTPS://WWW.ABOUTADS.INFO/APPCHOICES](http://www.aboutads.info/APPCHOICES) TO OPT-OUT IN MOBILE APPS.**

_**PLEASE NOTE** that all Cookie and Mobile opt-out tools referenced above are provided by third parties, not Intermarkets. Intermarkets does not control or operate these tools or the choices that advertisers and others provide through these tools._

### Third Party Websites

The Services may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties. Intermarkets does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our practices. If you click on a link or an advertisement, the privacy policy of the website to which you link will govern the collection and use of your information by that website’s operator(s). You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before disclosing any information to the website. For more information, please [click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/).

### Spyware or Adware

These terms refer to applications that are downloaded to your computer. These types of applications deliver ads (usually in the form of pop-up type ads) based on your web usage. We do not participate in any way with spyware or adware applications, and we do not download these types (or any types) of applications without your expressed acceptance. Cookies and .swf files are not spyware or adware, and they are not harmful to your computer.

### Public Forums

Please be advised that, whenever you voluntarily post information to any Intermarkets community page or any other public forums, such information can and may be accessed by the public. This means that any person or entity with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

### Security

We recognize the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. Accordingly, we employ standard security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect any information you transmit on or through the Site, please be advised that Intermarkets assumes no responsibility or liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond Intermarkets’ reasonable control.

### Processing in the United States

We process and store all information in the United States. By using our Services, you agree that the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.

### Children’s Privacy Statement

The Intermarkets Services are directed to, and intended for use by, adults only. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. Because we do not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Intermarkets may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown at the top of the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

When you use the Intermarkets Services, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and Intermarkets will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Intermarkets Services. You can also access, correct, or change your Personally Identifiable Information, or opt-out of our direct marketing efforts, by sending an email to [info@intermarkets.net](mailto:info@intermarkets.net). Once a request to opt out has been received, Intermarkets will send a confirming email message to the user that the user’s Personally Identifiable Information has been successfully opted out of Intermarkets’ database. If you do not receive this confirmatory email, then please contact us to ensure that your request was received and processed. If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [info@intermarkets.net](mailto:info@intermarkets.net) or send us a letter at Intermarkets, Inc., Attention: Privacy, 11951 Freedom Drive, 11th Floor, Reston, VA 20190.

### California Privacy Notice

California’s Shine the Light law provides California residents with the right to receive disclosures about any sharing of their personal information with other companies.

If you are a California resident and you provided your personal information to Intermarkets, then, once each calendar year, you may submit a written request for information about the information we shared, if any, with other companies for their use in direct marketing. To submit your written request, please email us at [info@intermarkets.net](mailto:info@intermarkets.net) or send us a letter at Intermarkets, Inc., Attention: Privacy, 11951 Freedom Drive, 11th Floor, Reston, VA 20190 with “Request for California Privacy” in the letter subject line.

Within 30 days of receiving your request, we will send you a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties.

We reserve our right not to respond to requests sent more than once in a calendar year, or requests submitted to an address other than the one posted in this notice.

Please note that the California Shine the Light law does not cover all information sharing. Our disclosure only includes information covered by the law.

### Users in the EEA and Switzerland

If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, the following information applies with respect to personal data collected through your use of our Services.

**Purposes of processing and legal basis for processing:**

We process personal data consistent with our disclosures in this Privacy Policy. We process personal data on the following legal bases: (1) with your consent; (2) as necessary to perform our agreement to provide the Services; and (3) as necessary for our legitimate interests in providing the Services where those interests do not override your fundamental rights and freedoms related to data privacy.

**Transfers**

Personal data we collect may be transferred to, and stored and processed in, the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates or processors maintain facilities. We will ensure that transfers of personal data to a third country or an international organization are subject to appropriate safeguards.

**Individual Rights**

If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, we respect your rights according to Chapter 3 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation. In order to verify your identity, we may require you to provide us with personal information prior to accessing any records containing information about you.
